Inventory of the Richard Wirthlin papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Incremental Reagan Books, 1968-1988 (Box 194-204)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Statewide Survey of Tennessee Voters, August 10-15, 1984 (Box 199)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Louisiana Presidential Study - Wave I, August 20-28, 1980 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Statewide Survey of Kentucky Voters, February 13-15, 1984 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Statewide Survey of Oklahoma Voters, February 23-25, 1984 (Box 202)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Statewide Survey of Massachusetts Voters, February 3-6, 1984 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Pennsylvania Statewide Survey, January 20-26, 1984 (Box 204)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Statewide Survey of Rhode Island Voters, January 23-24, 1984 (Box 199)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Mississippi, January 6-9, 1984 (Box 201)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Statewide Survey of Mississippi Voters, January 6-9, 1984 (Box 201)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Kentucky, July 10-12, 1984 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Focussed Group Interview Sessions: Mondale Attack advertising Post-Democratic Convention, July 1984 (Box 197)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attiitudes and Perceptions in the State of Kansas, July 3-10, 1984 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of South Carolina, June 12-13, 1984 (Box 199)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of New Jersey, June 15-17, 1984 (Box 202)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Ohio, June 16-18, 1984 (Box 202)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Ohio (II), June 16-18, 1984 (Box 202)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Alabama, June 1984 (Box 199)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Colorado, June 20-25, 1984 (Box 199)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Colorado, June 20-25, 1984 (Box 199)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Percpetions in the State of Texas, June 6-7, 1984 (Box 204)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Statewide Survey of Texas Voters, March 8-10, 1984 (Box 204)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Statewide Survey of New Jersey Voters, March 8-11, 1984 (Box 201)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Mississippi, May 1-6, 1984 (Box 201)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Statewide Survey of Mississippi Voters, May 1-6, 1984 (Box 201)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Focussed Group Interview Sessions: Pre-Convention Media for President Reagan, May 1984 (Box 197)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Indiana, May 30-Jun 6, 1984 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Main, May 3-16, 1984 (Box 201)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Main, May 3-16, 1984 (Box 201)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Maine, November 13-14, 1984 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Louisiana, Ocotober 27-28, 1984 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Missouri, October 10-13, 1984 (Box 201)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of North Carolina, October 11-15, 1984 (Box 202)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Georgia, October 12-13, 1984 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Arkansas, October 22-24, 1984 (Box 199)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Indiana, October 27-28, 1984 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Colorado, October 3-5, 1984 (Box 199)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Maine, October 4-7, 1984 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Tennessee, October 6-7, 1984 (Box 199)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Ohio (II), October 7-8, 1984 (Box 202)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Louisiana, October 8-10, 1984 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of New Jersey, October 8-9, 1984 (Box 202)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Deleware, October 9-10, 1984 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voters Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Connecticut, October 9-11, 1984 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Nebraska, October 9-11, 1984 (Box 201)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of West Virginia, October 9-13, 1984 (Box 204)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Louisiana Presidential Study - Wave II, September 12-15, 1980 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Colorado, September 14-18, 1984 (Box 199)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Deleware, September 16-22, 1984 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Alabama, September 1984 (Box 199)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of South Carolina, September 25-26, 1984 (Box 199)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Mississippi, September 27-29, 1984 (Box 201)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Main, September 28-29, 1984 (Box 201)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Maine, September 5-10, 1984 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Ohio (II), September 5-7, 1984 (Box 202)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Percpetions in the State of Texas, September 6-8, 1984 (Box 204)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Main, September 7-13, 1984 (Box 201)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Rhode Island, September 7-9, 1984 (Box 199)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Mississippi, September 7-9, 1984 (Box 201)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of New Jersey, September 7-9, 1984 (Box 202)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Kentucky, September 8-9, 1984 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84 Committee: Michigan Statewide Survey, August 11-15, 1984 (Box 198)
  - Reagan-Bush '84 Committee: Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Michigan, May, 1984 (Box 198)
  - Reagan-Bush Committee: Wyoming Statewide Study, September 1980 (Box 204)
  - Reagan for President Committee: Two Brushfire Surveys of New Hampshire Republican Voters, February 1980 (Box 196)
  - Reagan/Bush: National Panel, September 1980 (Box 196)
  - Reagan/Bush: National Panel, September 1980 (Box 196)
  - RNC: Themes and Issues for the 1982 Campaign, July 21, 1982 (Box 196)
  - RNC: Targeting, Scheduling and Communication Strategies for the 1982 Campaign, July 28, 1982 (Box 196)
  - RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, November 1982 (Box 196)
  - RNC: Catholics and Profiles, January 9, 1984 (Box 196)
  - RNC: Feasibility Report, April 1975 (Box 196)
  - RNC: Flash Results, April 21-23, 1987 (Box 197)
  - RNC: Nevada Brushfire, August 1985 (Box 197)
  - RNC: Flash Results: Farm States Study, Feb 16-17, 1985 (Box 197)
  - RNC: Aggregate Results, Feb 2-4, 1984 (Box 197)
  - RNC: RNC Farm States - Flash Results, Jan-Jun 1985 (Box 194)
  - RNC: Flash Results, Jan-Jun 1986 (Box 194)
  - RNC: Flash Results, Jan-Jun 1987 (Box 195)
  - RNC: Summary of National Attitudes, Jan-May 1981 (Box 199)
  - RNC: Ohio Statewide Study, January 1-7, 1980 (Box 202)
  - RNC: Texas Statewide Survey, January 5-10, 1981 (Box 204)
  - RNC: Flash Results, Jul-December 1986 (Box 194)
  - RNC: Flash Results, Jul-December 1987 (Box 195)
  - RNC: Aggregate Results, July 5-8, 1984 (Box 198)
  - RNC: Flash Results, July-December 1985 (Box 194)
  - RNC: National Post-Election Survey Flash Results, November 5-8, 1986 (Box 197)
  - RNC: Flash Results: Farm States Study, Oct 3-6, 1985 (Box 197)
  - RNC / Vice President George Bush: Flash Results and Subgroup Analysis of the April 21-23 National Monitor, May 8, 1987 (Box 197)
  - RNC 13: Flash Results, Sept 23-27, 1982 (Box 196)
  - RNC 83: Cross-Tabulations, January 9, 1984 (Box 197)
  - RNC Trax 85: Flash Results, January 12-14, 1985 (Box 196)
  - The Public Sector - San Francisco: Post-Election Focus Groups, November-December 1978 (Box 202)
  - Topline Report: Survey of American Attitudes Toward the Iran-Contras Situation, July 14, 1987 (Box 203)
  - VLT & Associates: Iowa Statewide Tracking, October 20-22, 1980 (Box 201)
  - A National Survey of Public Attitudes, December 1975 (Box 196)
  - Arizona Statewide Tracking, Oct 20-23, 1980 (Box 199)
  - Bush Abstracts - Bush & Reagan, 1977-1980 (Box 194)
  - Florida Statewide Post New Hampshire Convention, February 28, 1976 (Box 199)
  - Iranian Tracking, November 17-30 & December 1-14, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking, November 26-December 3, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking Flash Results, November 24, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking Flash Results, November 25, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking Flash Results, November 26, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking Flash Results, November 27, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking Flash Results, November 27, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking Flash Results, November 30, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking Flash Results, November 30, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking Flash Results, December 1, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking Flash Results, December 2, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking Flash Results, December 2, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking Flash Results, December 3, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking Flash Results, December 3, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking Flash Results, December 9, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking Flash Results, December 10, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking Flash Results, December 12, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking Flash Results, December 17, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking Flash Results, December 18, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking Flash Results, December 19, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking Flash Results, December 21, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking Flash Results, December 9-16, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking Flash Results, November 17-23, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking Flash Results, November 17-26, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking: Three Day Averages, November 26-December 10, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking: x-Tabs, December 9-10, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking: x-Tabs, November 17-December 9, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Iranian Tracking: x-tabs, November 26-December 3, 1986 (Box 203)
  - Michigan Tracking, October 1980 (Box 201)
  - National Brushfire, June 19-22 1986 (Box 203)
  - National Brushfire, July 18-21, 1986 (Box 197)
  - Nationwide Study - VP (Box 198)
  - New York Tracking, Oct 24-26, 1984 (Box 198)
  - Presidential Studies, October 7, 1980 (Box 201)
  - Presidential Studies, October 9, 1980 (Box 201)
  - Presidential Studies, October 11, 1980 (Box 201)
  - Presidential Studies, October 13, 1980 (Box 201)
  - Presidential Studies, August 20-28, 1980 (Box 201)
  - Presidential Studies, September 26-29, 1980 (Box 201)
  - Presidential Tracking, October 1980 (Box 202)
  - Presidnetial Trackings, October 23, 1980 (Box 200)
  - Reagan Image, undated (Box 198)
  - RFP National Run II, July 30, 1980 (Box 194)
  - Some Miscellaneous Research Projects of the 1984 Reagan-Bush Campaign, undated (Box 197)
  - Values & Psychographics Study, June 1979 (Box 195)
  - Values & Psychographics Study, June 1979 (Box 196)
  - White House Memorandums, August 5 1983 - September 2 1983 (Box 203)
  - White House Memorandums, December 8-20, 1983 (Box 203)
- Files, 1967-2005 (Box 205-250)
  Scope and Contents note
  Includes calendars, office files, collected reference material, interview documents, and material similar to that in the books. Arranged as received.
  - Day Timers, 1967-1989 (Box 205-210)
    - 1967-1969 (Box 205)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 205)
    - 1970-1972 (Box 205)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 206)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 206)
    - 1973-1975 (Box 206)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 207)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 207)
    - 1977-1979 (Box 207)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 208)
    - 1980, 1982 (Box 208)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 208)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 208)
    - 1985-1987 (Box 209)
    - 1984-1987 (Box 210)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 210)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 210)
  - Day Planners, 1989-2005 (Box 210-212)
    - November 1989-1990; UK 1990 (Box 210)
    - Circa 1990-1993; UK 1991-1992 (Box 211)
    - 1996-1998 (Box 211)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 212)
    - 2001-2004 (Box 212)
    - 2005 (Box 212)
  - Reagan, Ronald (Box 212-214)
    - Presidential campaign, 1976 (Box 212)
    - "Meeting with Ronnie,", March 29 (Box 212)
    - California (Box 212)
    - Florida (Box 212)
    - Illinois (Box 212)
    - New Hampshire (Box 212)
    - North Carolina (Box 212)
    - Clippings, 1976 January-June (Box 212)
    - Clippings, 1975 June-December (Box 213)
    - News summaries, 1975 (Box 213)
    - Reagan versus Ford clippings (Box 213)
    - 1975, September-December (4 folders) (Box 213)
    - 1976, January-August (8 folders) (Box 213)
    - "Did the Polls Go Wrong?", 1980 (Box 213)
    - Washington, Great American Family Program, 1983 June 22 (Box 213)
    - Washington, Los Angeles Times editorial board, 1983 June 22 (Box 213)
    - Washington, Government Research Corporation, 1983 June 28 (Box 213)
    - Washington, Harvard/ABC Symposium, 1983 September 30 (Box 213)
    - Thermometer rating: Nancy Reagan and Ronald Reagan, 1983 (Box 213)
    - California, RNC State Chairman's meeting, 1983 April 29 (Box 213)
    - Dallas, RNC Eagles meeting, 1983 June 9 (Box 213)
    - St. Louis, Mid-Continent States Caucus, 1983 June 6 (Box 213)
    - Toronto, Association of Canadian Advertisers, 1983 May 2 (Box 213)
    - Washington, Inside Washington, 1983 May 4 (Box 213)
    - Washington, NRSC Finance Committee meeting, 1983 May 5 (Box 213)
    - Washington, Sperling Breakfast, 1983 May 25 (Box 213)
    - Reagan legacy, undated (Box 213)
    - Pulseline Speech Analysis of Peace and National Security Address, 1986 February 26 (Box 213)
    - Carter opposition work for 1980 campaign (Box 213)
    - Transparencies, Presidential campaign, 1980 (Box 213)
    - Transparencies, Summary Points, 1980 (Box 213)
    - Address: President Ronald Reagan at the United Nations, 1985 October 31 (Box 213)
    - Presidential address: Peace and National Security, 1986 February 26 (Box 213)
    - Address: President Ronald Reagan at the United Nations, 1985 November 21 (Box 213)
    - "Americans' View of Life,", 1979 (Box 213)
    - 1998 Presentation, Western States primary (Box 213)
    - Miscellaneous Reagan articles, 1990s (Box 213)
    - 1981 Memo, Office of Statistical Policy and Standards, DIDS role and location (Box 213)
    - Miscellaneous newspaper articles, 1981 (Box 213)
    - First 90 Days Project, 1980 December 12 (Box 213)
    - Initial Actions Project/90 Days Project, 1981 January 12 (Box 213)
    - Transition notes, 1980 (Box 213)
    - Transition, 1980 November (Box 213)
    - Reagan focus groups, circa 1980 (2 folders) (Box 213)
    - Focus group 1 and 2, 1980 (2 folders) (Box 213)
    - Triangulation: Research in the Political Party paper, 1977 September 27 (Box 213)
    - Presidential Debates, 1980 (Box 213)
    - Transition News Summaries, Office of the President-Elect, 1980 December 11 - 1981 January 12 (Box 213)
    - National Merge, 1986 January-June (Box 214)
    - Republican National Committee (Box 214)
    - 1986 February-March (2 folders) (Box 214)
    - 1987 February-June (4 folders) (Box 214)
    - Reagan Job Rating, 1983-1985 (Box 214)
    - Geneva Summit, 1985 (Box 214)
    - Gramm/Rudman, 1985 (Box 214)
    - Republican National Committee (Box 214)
      - 1985 November Summit Tracking (Box 214)
      - 1985 November (Box 214)
      - 1986 Ad Testing (Box 214)
      - 1986 July, Study (Box 214)
      - 1986 August (Box 214)
      - 1986 September (Box 214)
      - 1986 October (Box 214)
  - Republican National Committee (Box 214-215)
    - Decision/Making/Information, 1987 (Box 214)
    - Pre-Election Study, 1988 October 31-November 2 (Box 214)
    - 1986 June Study (Box 214)
    - Republican Party Institutional Ads, 1982-1983 (Box 214)
    - DMI (Decision Making Information) and RNC meeting, 1986 June 11 (Box 214)
    - Weekly reports, 1986 April-July (Box 214)
    - 1986 May (Box 214)
    - 1987 (Box 214)
    - General, 1988 (Box 214)
    - 1986, Day after Ad Test (Box 214)
    - 1987 March (Box 214)
    - 1987 July (Box 214)
    - 1987 September (2 folders) (Box 214)
    - 1987 October, Summit Focus Group (Box 214)
    - 1987 October (Box 214)
    - Contras/American Public Opinion, 1987 (Box 214)
    - 1987 November (Box 214)
    - Pre-Summit Monitor, 1987 November (Box 214)
    - 1987 December Cross Section (Box 215)
    - Astrology, 1988 (Box 215)
    - 1988 January-May (5 folders) (Box 215)
    - General, 1981-1985 (Box 215)
    - Communications Division. Network: Voices For Victory: Operating Manual, undated (Box 215)
    - RNC meeting, presentation materials, 1983 January 29 (Box 215)
    - Republican Study Committee: What's the Matter with Democratic Foreign Policy? 1984 May 7 (Box 215)
    - Monthly Calendar of Events, 1985 (Box 215)
    - Illinois Political Briefing, 1984 May 25 (Box 215)
  - Ronald Reagan speeches, 1976 (Box 215)
  - Ronald Reagan speeches, 1981 (Box 215)
  - State of the Union (Box 215-216)
    - Memos, 1981-1987 (Box 215)
    - 1982 (Box 215)
    - Drafts, 1986 (Box 215)
    - 1986 (Box 215)
    - Address/Inaugural, 1984 (Box 215)
    - 1987. Includes background materials (Box 216)
    - 1988. Includes background materials (Box 216)
  - Reagan/Bush letterhead, circa 1980 (Box 216)
  - Ronald Reagan, Joint Session Speech, 1981 (Box 216)
  - Reagan Speech, 1982 (Box 216)
  - Ronald Reagan Presidential Foundation, 1986-1987 (Box 216)
  - Reagan midterm, 1982 (Box 216)
  - Reagan/Bush, 1984 (Box 216)
  - 1986 January-May (5 folders) (Box 216)
  - Triangulation, 1979-1980 (Box 216)
  - Announcement speech, Focus Groups, 1979 (Box 216)
  - Study Prepared for National Republican Congressional Committee, 1982 March (Box 216)
  - Data for Simulation Model from National Survey, Reagan/Bush 1984 (Box 216)
  - Ronald Reagan speeches, 1983 (Box 216)
  - Central America speech, 1984 (Box 216)
  - White House staffing memoranda, 1984 (Box 216)
  - Children's Aid Society of Utah, 1985 (Box 216)
  - Ronald Reagan speeches, 1985-1987 (Box 216)
  - Speech files, Bush/Quayle, 1988 (Box 216)
  - Pre-Election memos, 1988 (Box 217)
  - Pre-Election clippings, 1988 (Box 217)
  - Post-Election analysis, 1988 (Box 217)
  - Reorganization, 1980 March (Box 217)
  - Strategic Considerations report, 1980 March 28 (Box 217)
  - Constituencies (General), 1984 (Box 217)
  - White House Staffing memos, 1984 (Box 217)
  - Meeting with President Reagan, 1988 February 5 (Box 217)
  - Meeting with the President, 1988 March 7 (Box 217)
  - Survey, 1988 April 14 (Box 217)
  - Meeting with President Reagan, 1988 May 17 (Box 217)
  - Meeting with Ronald Reagan, 1988 June 15 (Box 217)
  - Meeting with Ronald Reagan, 1989 February 13 (Box 217)
  - Meeting with Chris Arterton, 1989 April 17 (Box 217)
  - Visit with President and Mrs. Reagan, 1990 July 3 (Box 217)
  - Ronald Reagan, Conversation with Press, 1991 March 22 (Box 217)
  - President Ronald Reagan, miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 217)
  - National, RNC, 1984 (Box 217)
  - Campaign memos, 1988 (Box 217)
  - Survey, 1988 (Box 217)
  - "Super Tuesday" night, 1988 (Box 217)
  - RNC National Flash Results, 1988 (Box 217)
  - Central America, 1984 (Box 217)
  - Coalitions: Blacks, 1984 (Box 217)
  - Issues: Baby Boomers, 1984 (Box 217)
  - White House strategy meetings, 1984 (Box 217)
  - Personal and Public Perspectives on the Reagan Presidency, by Richard B. Wirthlin, 1991 (Box 217)
  - Newspapers and magazines, 1980-1984 (Box 217)
  - Memoranda, 1987-1988 (Box 217)
  - Transparencies, charts and graphs, 1984 (Box 218)
  - Colin Powell, 1994 (Box 218)
  - Post Election clippings, 1980 (Box 218)
  - Debates file, 1980 (Box 218)
  - League of Women Voters, 1980 (Box 218)
    - Baltimore negotiations, 1980 (Box 218)
    - Baltimore strategy, 1980 (Box 218)
    - Baltimore debate, 1980 (Box 218)
    - Baltimore post-debate, 1980 (Box 218)
    - Cleveland negotiations, 1980 (Box 218)
    - Cleveland debate, 1980 (Box 218)
    - Cleveland strategy, 1980 (Box 218)
    - Post debate, Cleveland, 1980 (Box 218)
    - Back-up materials, 1980 (Box 218)
  - Exhibits Use of Survey Research in the Decision Making Process of the Reagan Presidential Campaign, presented by Richard W. Wirthlin to the 36th Annual Conference, American Association for Public Opinion Research, 1981 May 28 (Box 218)
  - Newspapers and magazines. Includes photos of Ronald Reagan, Nancy Reagan, and others, 1984 (Box 218)
  - Democrats, 1985 (Box 218)
  - Issue: Bitburg, 1985 (Box 218)
  - Colin Powell backup, 1995 (Box 218)
  - Colin Powell, weekly memos, 1995-1996 (Box 218)
  - Public Attitudes toward Nancy Reagan, 1980-1983, survey, 1988 (Box 218)
  - Memoranda, 1983-1988 (Box 218)
  - Nancy Reagan, 1984 (Box 218)
  - Meeting with Nancy Reagan, 1985 February 20 (Box 218)
  - Nancy Reagan (Box 218)
    - 1985-1989 (Box 218)
    - 1986 (Box 218)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 218)
    - 1988 (Box 218)
    - 1989 (Box 218)
  - Ronald Reagan personal letters, 1990, 1994 (Box 218)
  - U.S. National study, volume 1, 1976 July (Box 218)
  - State studies, 1980 May-June (Box 218)
  - Presidential tracking study, 1980 (Box 218)
  - U.S. National study, 1981 (Box 218)
  - Congressional District post-election study, 1982 November (Box 219)
  - Market Opinion research, Mississippi 2nd CD Data, 1982 September (Box 219)
  - Market Opinion research, U.S. National Study #2, 1983 June (Box 219)
  - King, Larry, undated (Box 219)
  - Journalists, 1981 (Box 219)
  - Kaiser, Bob, Washington Post, 1981-1984 (Box 219)
  - Klein, Herb, San Diego Union, 1982 (Box 219)
  - Journalists, 1983-1988 (Box 219)
  - Ellis, John, NBC News, 1982-1986 (Box 219)
  - Donaldson, Sam, 1983 (Box 219)
  - Kraft, Joseph, 1983 (Box 219)
  - Evans-Novak, 1983-1988 (Box 219)
  - Journalists, 1984 (Box 219)
  - Lambro, Donald, United Features Syndicate, New York, 1986-1987 (Box 219)
  - Meet the Press - NBC, 1987 July 19 (Box 219)
  - Journalist, interview with Jane Mayer, 1987 June 11 (Box 219)
  - Journalists, 1987 (Box 219)
  - Clippings, 1979-1984 (Box 219)
  - Journalists: George Will, 1981 (Box 219)
  - Barnes, Fred, undated (Box 219)